<resources>
    <string name="app_name">emplyApp</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="currency">Currency</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">
            <p>At Emply, we value and respect the privacy of our users. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and disclose information when you use our mobile application [App Name]. By using the [App Name], you consent to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.</p>
            <h2>Collection and Use of Information</h2>
            <p>We collect information about you when you use the [App Name]. This includes:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Information you provide directly to us, such as your name, email address, and other contact information.</li>
                <li>Information we collect automatically when you use the [App Name], such as your IP address, device type, browser type, and usage information.</li>
            </ul>
            <p>We may use the information we collect to:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Provide and improve our services.</li>
                <li>Communicate with you about our services, including sending you promotional messages and offers.</li>
                <li>Monitor and analyze usage and trends.</li>
                <li>Comply with legal obligations.</li>
            </ul>
            <h2>Sharing of Information</h2>
            <p>We may share your information with third-party service providers who help us provide and improve our services. These service providers are contractually obligated to protect your information and are not authorized to use or disclose your information for any other purpose.</p>
            <p>We may also share your information in the following circumstances:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>With your consent or at your direction.</li>
                <li>In response to a subpoena, court order, or other legal request.</li>
                <li>To protect our rights, property, or safety, or the rights, property, or safety of others.</li>
                <li>In connection with a merger, acquisition, or other corporate transaction.</li>
            </ul>
            <h2>Data Security</h2>
            <p>We take reasonable measures to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, and misuse. However, no security measure is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee the security of your information.</p>
            <h2>Your Choices</h2>
            <p>You may update or correct the information we have about you by contacting us at [Contact Email]. You may also opt out of receiving promotional messages from us by following the instructions in those messages.</p>
            <h2>Changes to this Privacy Policy</h2>
            <p>We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.</p>
            <h2>Contact Us</h2>
            <p>If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [Contact Email].</p>
    </string>
    <string name="terms_of_service">

    </string>
    <string name="about_us">
            <p>Emply is a job finder app designed to help job seekers find the perfect job and employers find the perfect candidate. With a user-friendly interface and advanced search features, Emply makes it easy to find and apply for jobs.</p>
            <h2>Features</h2>
            <ul>
                <li>Search for jobs by location, job title, and company.</li>
                <li>Save your favorite job listings.</li>
                <li>Apply for jobs directly from the app.</li>
                <li>Get notified when new jobs are posted.</li>
                <li>Create a profile and upload your resume.</li>
                <li>View job application history.</li>
                <li>Contact employers directly through the app.</li>
            </ul>
            <h2>Contact Us</h2>
            <p>If you have any questions about Emply or need help using the app, please contact us at [Contact Email].</p>
    </string>
</resources>